fullpricenever.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy | It's a Lovely Life!

Looking for our TOS/Terms and Conditions? You can find them [here](https://itsalovelylife.com/tos/).

 **Sale Pros Corp Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://itsalovelylife.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

    – “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

    – “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

    – “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

    – Facebook Pixel, Google Analytics code, Pinterest Pixel are used to collect data

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the information you provide to us, ie. email address and name to:

Communicate with you;

When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We never share your Personal Information with third parties.

We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful requests for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

    FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

    GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

    BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

MINORS

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13.

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at reese@itsalovelylife.com or by mail using the details provided below:

  PO BOX 1243, Bonsall, CA, 92003, United States

 **Additional Information we want you to know:**

We do not intentionally target people in the EU as readers of our blog, email list subscribers, or as customers for our courses. However, we are still taking the following steps to protect the privacy of all of our reader and customers. We will continue to do our absolute best to always consider the privacy of our valued readers and customers.

We want you to know that we have Google Analytics and Facebook Pixels installed. You can read more about both of those on their respective sites to learn more about what they collect, link below. We offer mailing list options too. When you provide your email address to us for one of our courses, quick guides, or for our regular email newsletter, we will add you to our mail email list and you will occasionally be sent an email with a broad range of topics from blogging, to travel, to family life and more. If you provide your email address to us for any reason via one of these signups, you will be subscribed to our email list. You can opt out at any time by using the unsubscribe link on all of our emails.

We have never and will never sell our email list.

Occasionally we have sponsored posts and sponsored content on our site. The companies that advertise on our site will often have their own tracking code that we add to each sponsored post. We also have affiliate links on our site. These links allow tracking of clicks on certain links and if you purchase something using these links we earn a commission at no cost to you. I have listed these companies below and I will be updating this list often.

Links to privacy policies:

Google: https://policies.google.com/privacy

Gravatar: https://automattic.com/privacy/

Facebook: https://facebook.com/about/privacyshield

Constant Contact: https://www.constantcontact.com/legal/privacy-statement

Amazon: https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/
